Let's cover the PIMBOC guide processes and
stakeholder management.
So if you're looking at your process map
or process matrix on page 25 of the
PIMBOC, you will see that in initiating as
we're getting our project or phase
started, we develop the project charter
and identify stakeholders.
It's imperative we know who the
stakeholders are as early as possible.
and we will do this throughout the
project.
Then we'll move into planning.
We'll plan stakeholder engagement and
communications.
Who needs what, when, where, why,
how.
We'll keep planning, creating the pieces
of our puzzle, and then we'll keep going
through the rest of the planning processes
until we develop our least initial
references for scope, time and cost
baselines.
We're baselines.
We'll move into executing to do the work
of the project according to the plan.
So again, our plan will state how we'll
manage stakeholder engagement.
Again, this is where we will be building
the relationships, engaging, involving our
stakeholders on our project, in the
meetings, in making decisions.
then as soon as we're baseline we start
executing and controlling comparing the
plan to data actuals we're looking for any
variance so we need to make sure that our
communications that involving engaging the
stakeholders is working to get them to
support our project there are no official
closing process processes.